<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Robert Colley Blog</title>
        <link>https://robertjcolley.com/blog</link>
        <description>Robert Colley Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Me]]></title>
            <link>https://robertjcolley.com/blog/2022/04/16/about-me</link>
            <guid>/2022/04/16/about-me</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hi! My name is Robert Colley. Check out what I'm working on!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi! My name is Robert Colley. Check out what I&#x27;m working on!</p><h2>Work</h2><p>I pride myself on using my knowledge and skills in a way where I can make a difference. So far, my young career has been in health and medical technology. I love to lead teams and create products which work by putting the user first.</p><ul><li>Hologic ThinPrep Genesis Review Station (pre-production)</li><li><a href="https://nextstep.health">NextStep.Health</a> - Director of Engineering</li><li><a href="https://nextstepgoodlife.com">NextStep GoodLife</a> - Director of Engineering</li></ul><h2>Running</h2><ul><li>I am currently training for a half marathon!</li><li>Half Marathon: 2:30 PR</li></ul><h2>Lifting</h2><p>All time 1RMs:</p><ul><li>Bench: 230 lbs</li><li>Squat: 275lbs</li><li>DeadLift: 405lbs</li><li>OHP: 155 lbs</li></ul><h2>Chess</h2><p><a href="https://www.chess.com/member/bobbycolley">Bobby Colley (bobbycolley) - Chess Profile</a></p><ul><li>Currently rated 600 ELO</li></ul><h2>Skiing</h2><ul><li>I only fall a few times per trip</li><li>Favorite mountain: Sunapee</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is my plan?]]></title>
            <link>https://robertjcolley.com/blog/2022/02/24/what-is-my-plan</link>
            <guid>/2022/02/24/what-is-my-plan</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Often times you get asked about "What is your 5 year plan?" and I have NO idea about specifics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Often times you get asked about &quot;What is your 5 year plan?&quot; and I have NO idea about specifics.</p><p>As of right now, I know:</p><h2>1. I want to start my own business</h2><p>I know I can run a successful business. I am very detail oriented and I have a lot of experience &quot;running&quot; a team to create a product. I have made mistakes and have been overextended, but with one sole product and enough time, I know that I can create a product that will be successful.</p><h2>2. I might need to go back to school to get an MBA</h2><p>I don&#x27;t know everything I need to know to start a good business. I can create a decent software product, but I don&#x27;t know how to create a successful business from a software product.</p><h2>3. I don&#x27;t have a good idea for a business that I want to commit to</h2><p>One of the ideas I&#x27;ve had before is a &quot;social wellness&quot; platform. It would be very similar to <a href="https://nextstepgoodlife.com">NextStep GoodLife</a>, but I don&#x27;t really want to make another social media app. I&#x27;ve thought about making a fitness tracking app, but that is a super saturated market and I don&#x27;t want to be in it. I thought about &quot;party tech&quot; but there isn&#x27;t a huge market for scalability - just frat bros and sorority girls in that market. That would include party planning apps, which is somewhat niche. I&#x27;ve also thought about creating a javascript teaching platform, something in crypto, or something else entirely.</p><p>Eesha had an idea to see everything about her health records in one place by connecting portals together. I don&#x27;t know how to monetize this.</p><p>TLDR; Ideas list:</p><ul><li>Create a social wellness platform</li><li>Create a fitness tracking app</li><li>Create a party planning app</li><li>Create a teaching platform</li><li>Create a something in crypto</li><li>Create a health records app</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>